HERE General Executive Board Files 6199/006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE General Executive Board Files
1928-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/006
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
8254422
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 11, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: All 6199 Collections
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; UNITE HERE (Organizaiton)
8254422
- Propositions and Minutes (Box 1)
  - General Executive Board Propositions, 1928-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General Executive Board Minutes, 1955-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - G.E.B. Listing Book Propositions, 1954-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - G.E.B. Listing Book Propositions, 1963-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - G.S.T. John Gibson Listing Book Propositions I-3158, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - G.E.B. Propositions, 1982-1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - G.E.B. Propositions, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - G.S.T. G.E.B. Propositions, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - G.E.B. Propositions, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - G.E.B. Propositions, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - G.E.B. Minutes, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - G.E.B. Minutes, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - G.E.B. Minutes, 1964-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - G.E.B. Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - G.E.B. Minutes, 1976-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - G.E.B. Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - G.E.B. Minutes, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)